Guide to the Papers of Mordecai Sheftall (1735-1797), undated, 1761-1867, 1873, 1932, 1941 (bulk 1777-1778) *P-12
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: American Revolutionary and Continental Troop Commissarial Work and Provision Return Records, undated, 1777-1779, 1782-1783
  - Series II: Commissarial Records - Army, undated, 1777-1778
    - Subseries II: Provision Returns 2nd Regiment and 2nd Battalion, undated, 1777-1778
      - (Binder 5)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for No Sergeants, Seventeen Privates, Eight Women, and Nine Children, 07/10/1778 (Item 169)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright to [Matthew Roach] for Those Belonging to Samuel Elbert's Command, 07/12/1778-07/21/1778 (Item 170)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter, 07/14/1778 (Item 171)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Seventeen Privates, Eight Women, and Nine Children, 07/14/1778 (Item 172)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Five Men and One Woman, 07/14/1778-07/17/1778 (Item 173)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright from 07/11/1778-07/16/1778, 07/15/1778 (Item 174)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for John Foster, 07/16?/1778 (Item 175)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Twenty-two Privates, Nine Women and Nine Children, 07/17/1778 (Item 176)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Regiment Signed by Shadrack Wright for Six Men, 07/17/1778 (Item 177)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Capt. [?] Company, 07/21/1778 (Item 178)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright and Daniel Handel for Ten Men, 07/17/1778-07/21/1778 (Item 179)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright to Thomas [?] for One Sargeant and One Private, 07/21/1778 (Item 180)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for No Sergeants, Forty Privates, Ten Women and Nine Children, 07/21/1778 (Item 181)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp for the Fifth Company, 07/22/1778-07/27/1778 (Item 182)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Wandin for John Wandin, Anthony Marten from 04/[01]/1778-05/[01]/1778, 07/22/1778 (Item 183)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Sergeants, Forty-eight Privates, Ten Women, and Nine Children, 07/23/1778 (Item 184)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright to [Illegible] for Back Rations for Seven Men, 07/24/1778-07/29/1778 (Item 185)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and George Hancock for Five Days, 07/24/1778-07/29/1778 (Item 186)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and [John Willams?] for One Woman, One Man, and One Child of the Seventh Company, 07/25/1778-08/01/1778 (Item 187)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Eleven Privates, Four Women, and One Child, 07/25/[1778] (Item 188)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp for Two Men of Capt. Miller's Company, 07/25/1778 (Item 189)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Sergeants, Forty-five Privates, Ten Women, and Nine Children, 07/25/1778 (Item 190)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp for One Man, 07/26/1778-07/30/1778 (Item 191)
        - Provision Return for the [2nd Battalion?] Signed by Samuel Camp for Lt. Col. Bailly, 07/27/1778-08/01/1778 (Item 192)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Three Sergeants, Fifty-five Privates, Sixteen Woman, and Ten Children, 07/27/1778-08/01/1778 (Item 193)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Three Men and One Woman, 07/27/1778-08/01/1778 (Item 194)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Man, 07/27/1778 (Item 195)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shadrack Wright for Five Sergeants, Sixty-eight Privates, Sixteen Women and Ten Children, 07/29/1778 (Item 196)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for One Soldier, 07/29/1778 (Item 197)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp for Six [Illegible], Two Officers, Thirty-nine Privates, and Two Women, 07/30/1778 (Item 198)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp for One Man Belonging to Captain Edward Wood's Company, 07/20/1778-07/30/1778 (Item 199)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and John Strong, Surgeon, 07/31/1778-08/03/1778 (Item 200)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and Daniel Roberts, 08/01/1778-08/12/1778 (Item 201)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and Daniel Roberts to Robert Howe, 08/03/1778-08/31/1778 (Item 202)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp for "four from Sunbury", 08/04/1778-08/06/1778 (Item 203)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp to Samuel Camp [Fragment], 08/07/1778 (Item 204)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp to Abraham Jones, 08/09/[1778] (Item 205)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Regiment Signed by Samuel Camp Thomas Davenport, John Strong, Robert Howe, and E. Wood for Private James Connelly, 08/10/1778-09/10/1778 and 10/05/1778-10/26/1778 (Item 206)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by D.L. Roberts for [William] Willson of the Seventh Company, 08/20/1778-08/31/1778 (Item 207)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Camp and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 08/21/1778-08/24/1778 (Item 208)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Daniel Roberts for George Hancock, 08/24/1778-08/26/1778 (Item 209)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Camp and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 08/24/1778-08/25/1778 (Item 210)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall to William [Turner], 08/25/1778; WPA_H-0044; Indexed #052 (Item 211)
        - Rations for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and Daniel Roberts to John Wilson for Rations Due from 12/31/1777-08/30/1778, 08/27/1778 (Item 212)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and [Benjamin Moore] to William Turner, 08/27/1778-10/20/1778 (Item 213)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Camp and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 08/26/1778-08/27/1778 (Item 214)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Camp and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 08/28/1778-08/30/1778 (Item 215)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall to James Hill for the Balance of Back Rations Due from 03/02/1778-08/1778, 08/31/1778 (Item 216)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for William Gunn, 08/31/1778-09/30/1778 (Item 217)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and D.L. Roberts for Frederick Shick, 08/17/1778-08/31/1778 (Item 218)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Major Porter, One Servant and One Soldier, 09/1778 (Item 219)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Camp and Sheftall Sheftall for Thomas Pain from 12/15/1777-08/01/1778, 09/02/1778 (Item 220)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by D.L. Roberts for Two Men in Capt. Cunningham's Company, 09/02/1778 (Item 221)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall for Back Order Rations Due to Thomas Porter from 12/15/1777- 08/01/1778, 09/03/1778; WPA_G-0242; Indexed #048 (Item 222)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall for Rations Due John Clarke from 06/02/1778-08/01/1778, 09/03/1778 (Item 223)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by D.L. Roberts for Washerwomen and Children of the Second Company, 09/04/1778 (Item 224)
        - Provision Return Certification for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall for Capt. [?] Mosby [Fragment], 09/04/1778 (Item 225)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/04/1778-09/06/1778 (Item 226)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Sheftall Sheftall for Back Rations [Fragment], 09/[05]/1778 (Item 227)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by D.L. Roberts for Sixty-nine Men of the [First] Company, 09/04/1778-09/06/1778 (Item 228)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for Capt. Miller, 09/06/1778-09/13/1778 (Item 229)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for One Man in Capt. Francis Moore's Company, 09/07/1778 (Item 230)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Edward Wood with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/07/1778-09/08/1778 (Item 231)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Unsigned for the First Company Commanded by Col. Elbert with Numbers of Persons Provided For, 09/08/1778 (Item 232)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/09/1778-09/10/1778 (Item 233)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for One Woman Belonging to Capt. Wood's Company, 09/11/[1778] (Item 234)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for [Edward] Wood, 09/11/1778 (Item 235)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/11/1778-09/13/1778 (Item 236)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by D.L. Roberts for Col. Roberts, 09/12/1778 (Item 237)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/14/1778-09/15/1778 (Item 238)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for Frederick Shick, 09/16/1778 (Item 239)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/16/1778-09/17/1778 (Item 240)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Samuel Elbert and James Hill for Archibald Adams "Going out of town for a particular service" for the Fifth Company, 09/18/1778 (Item 241)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and D.L. Roberts to Cornelius Collins, 09/18?/1778 (Item 242)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/18/1778-09/20/1778 (Item 243)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by D.L. Roberts and the Mark of Benjamin Lindsay for Benjamin Lindsay for One Man of the Fifth Company, 09/21/1778 (Item 244)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/21/1778 (Item 245)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/23/1778-09/24/1778 (Item 246)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/25/1778-09/27/1778 (Item 247)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for the [?] Company, 09/26/1778-09/30/1778 (Item 248)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for John Morrison and One Bowman, 09/28/1778 (Item 249)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and D.L. Roberts with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/28/1778-09/29/1778 (Item 250)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Col. Roberts, Major Porter and Three Servants, 09/29/1778 (Item 251)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Henry Allison, 09/30/1778 (Item 252)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for Robert Howe, 09/30/1778 (Item 253)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Francis Moore for Robert Howe, 09/30/1778-10/31/1778 (Item 254)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 09/30/1778 (Item 255)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Col. Roberts, Maj. Porter and Three Servants, 10/1778 (Item 256)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Francis Moore for Frederick Shick, 10/[?]/1778-10/30/1778 (Item 257)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Edward Wood for J. Adam Alexander, 10/01/1778 (Item 258)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for Edward Hood, 10/01/1778 (Item 259)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and John Roberts for Cornelius Collins, 10/01/1778 (Item 260)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Companies Provided for, 10/01/1778 (Item 261)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe to Abraham Jones, 10/01/1778-10/31/1778 (Item 262)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Edward Wood for William Gunn of the First Company, 10/01/1778-11/01/1778 (Item 263)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by James Hill for One Man of the Fifth Company, 10/03/1778 (Item 264)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe for Capt. Miller, 10/05/1778 (Item 265)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Col. Roberts, Maj. Porter and Three Servants, 10/05/1778 (Item 266)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 10/05/1778-10/06/1778 (Item 267)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and John Roberts for John Morrison, 10/06/1778 (Item 268)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter to Mr. Camp for Twelve Pounds of Beef Back Rations for Benjamin Porter, 10/07/1778 (Item 269)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Col. Roberts, Majors Porter and Lane and Three Servants, 10/07/1778 (Item 270)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and James Hill for One Man in the Fifth Company, 10/07/1778 (Item 271)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Benjamin Porter for Edward Hood, 10/09/1778 (Item 272)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Regiment Signed by Robert Howe and Benjamin Porter for John Morrison, 10/10/1778 (Item 273)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe with List of Officers and Staff Numbers, 10/10/1778-10/18/1778 (Item 274)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for One Barrel of Flour Charged to Col. Roberts, Major [Joseph] Lane, and Major B. Porter, 10/12/1778; WPA_G-0027; Indexed #017 (Item 275)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Benjamin Porter for Capt. Cunningham, 10/12/1778 (Item 276)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter, 10/13/1778 (Item 277)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for Col. Roberts, Major Porter and [James Kane?] and Three Servants, 10/13/1778 (Item 278)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Benjamin Porter with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 10/13/1778-10/15/1778 (Item 279)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Wandin for John Wandin in the Seventh Company (Two Returns), 10/01/1778-10/30/1778 (Item 280)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Benjamin Porter for John Morrison, 10/16/1778 (Item 281)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter for a Soldier and Major Porter's Servant, 10/17/1778 (Item 282)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Samuel Elbert for John Morrison, 10/19/1778 (Item 283)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Benjamin Porter with List of Officers and Staff Numbers, 10/19/1778-10/20/1778 (Item 284)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by [Torn] with List of Officers and Staff Numbers, 10/21/1778-10/22/1778 (Item 285)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe and Francis Moore for John Morrison, 10/22/1778 (Item 286)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong with List of Companies Provided for, 10/23/1778 (Item 287)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Francis Moore and Robert Howe with List of Officers and Staff Numbers [Torn], 10/23/1778-10/25/1778 (Item 288)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Francis Moore with List of Officers and Staff Numbers, 10/26/1778-10/27/1778 (Item 289)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion with List of Officers and Staff Numbers Signed by Robert Howe and Francis Moore with List of Officers and Staff [Torn], 10/28/1778-10/29/1778 (Item 290)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd [Battalion] Signed by Illegible with Partial List of Those Provided for [Fragment], 11/02/1778 (Item 291)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe with List of Officers and Staff Numbers [Fragment], 11/10/1778-10/12/1778 (Item 292)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe for John Morrison, 11/13/1778 (Item 293)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by John Strong and Benjamin Porter for William D. Strother from 09/04/1778-30/1778, (10/14/1778), 11/19/1778 (Item 294)
        - Provision Return for the 2nd Battalion Signed by James [Hull] for One Washerwoman and Child of the Second Company [Fragment], 11/24/[1778] (Item 295)
    - Subseries III: Provision Returns for the 3rd Regiment and 3rd Battalion, undated, 1777-1778
      This Subseries contains 328 Provision Returns signed to either the 3rdRegiment or the 3rdBattalion. A partial list of recurring names of officers and non-coms in this Subseries are: John Stirk, Joseph Lane, Robert Howe, John Frazer, Nathaniel Pearce, Thomas Threadgill, Shem Cook, John Peter Wagon [Wagnon], Robert Rae, Charles Clarke, James Scriven, John Jeter, Daniel Roberts, Thomas Lane, John McIntosh, William Lowe, John Dumouchel, Rains Cook, Josiah Hatton, John Phillips, William Scott, Shadrack Wright, James Walton, Thomas Davenport, William Wash, John Walton, Thomas Phillips, William Wash, Gideon Booker, Isaac Hicks, and the mark of Molly Johnston. Captain's companies represented by name are Lane's, Smith's, Scott's, Nash's and Downman's, while the Eighth and Vacant Companies are also mentioned by name. Several of the Provision Returns are for Officers and Non-Coms stationed at Captain Read's Plantation (Read's Bluff), Fort Howe, and men going to Sunbury. Some returns include lists of names and numbers of persons provided for. Several unnamed subaltern soldiers, washerwomen, men, and children are also mentioned in many of the Provision Returns for the 3rdRegiment and 3rdBattalion.
      - (Binder 6)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Agreeable to John Stirk and Received by the Mark of Milly Johnston for Johnston and Child, undated (Item 1)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Battalion Signed by Burrel Smith for Burrel Smith for Molasses, undated (Item 2)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Battalion Signed by Joseph Lane for Four Men Commanded by Capt. Wall, undated (Item 3)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Battalion Signed by Robert Howe for Two Men [Fragment], undated (November 1778?) (Item 4)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Battalion Unsigned for John Frazer, Nathaniel Pearce, and Thomas Threadgill for Provisions Due (Three Returns), undated (Item 5)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Battalion Signed by Shem Cook for [Illegible], Three Sergeants, and Thirty-seven Rank and File with note on verso: "as you have no Fresh Provisions [Torn] and don't know what [Illegible] will make to give Out the Salt [pro]visions as the Troops must be supplied", undated (Item 6)
        - Provision Return Signed by John Peter Wagon to [Illegible], undated (Item 7)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon and [Robert] Rae to Thomas [Torn], [00]/[15]/1777-03/02/[1778] (Item 8)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to Charles Clarke [Torn], 11/20/1777-02/20/1778 (Item 9)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to Isaac Hicks (Three Returns), 12/13/1777-05/12/1778 (Item 10)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to Richard Spark of the Eighth Company, 12/14/1777-03/14/1778 (Item 11)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by Dan [Koburth] to John Peter Wagon, 12/15/1777-02/15/1778 (Item 12)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon for Randolph Smith of the [Eighth] Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 13)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon for Thomas Weden of the Seventh Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 14)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to Abraham Watson of the Seventh Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 15)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to D.L. Roberts, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 16)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to David Rainie of Seventh Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 17)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to Ebenezer Callander, 12/15/1777-02/23/1778 (Item 18)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to George Bevill of the First Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 19)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to George Turner in the Fifth Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 20)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to James Oliver, Drummer of the First Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (04/06/1778) (Item 21)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon to John Boyd of the Seventh Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 22)
        - Provision Return for the 3rd Regiment Signed by John Peter Wagon and [Robert] Rae to John Chamberlain of Capt. Hick's Company, 12/15/1777-03/15/1778 (Item 23)